Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 99 records 1947-2002 IBT0034
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 99 records
1947-2002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0034
0.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains the records of International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 99 of Louisville, Kentucky. This local is part of the International Mailers Union of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Materials include agreements between Local 99 and various publishing agencies, as well as by-laws, joint council reports, and organizational letters of the Local itself.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, [2012] [2012.80].
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the records of International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 99 of Louisville, Kentucky. This local is part of the International Mailers Union of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Materials include agreements between Local 99 and various publishing agencies, as well as by-laws, joint council reports, and organizational letters of the Local itself.
Arrangement
Organized into 1 series.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Labor; Labor unions -- Kentucky -- History -- 20th century
- Agreements, September 1994 - Marc 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreements - By and between Courier Journal and Louisville Mailers, December 1990 - November 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agreements - By and between Standard Grovure and Louisville Mailers, February 1988 - Feberuary 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agreements - Standard Gravure and Louisville Mailers, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- By Laws - Kentucky-West Virginia Conference of Teamsters, n.d.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Priority Objectives and lists, 1958; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Priority Commitee Reports, 1947-1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Priority Ballots, 17 May 1950; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Joint Council - Category 3 Women Stackers, 23 March 1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Joint Council - Local 89's Attempted Takeover, April - June 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Report - Executive report Gannett Co. inc., Janaury 1996 - May 1997; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Report - Fire Inspection Report, Janaury 2002; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- International Mailers Union Delegates, 13-17 August 1960; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Teamsters KY Governor Election, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Graphs of Profits, 1983; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Organizational Letters and leaflet Material, March 1982; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- The Strike in Detroit, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lost Time Forms, n.d.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)